findlocalweather.com 2017-11-24

# Find Local Weather Privacy Policy

We care about your privacy. We want to tell you in detail about the Internet policies and practices which we have adopted to protect your privacy so that you can feel confident about how we handle the personal information you entrust to us online. The server(s) that make(s) this site available may be located outside the country from which you accessed this site, but we will collect, process and use personal information only in accordance with this policy.

While we do not intend to make changes to our policies very often, it is always a good idea to double check when you visit our site to be sure that you have read and agree with our most current policy statement. We will not make any changes that have retroactive effect unless legally required to do so.

The content on our sites may include, among other items of interest, entertainment, games, recipes, surveys, sweepstakes, and contests, and may also include advertising and opportunities to shop online. We may also provide information on our company and our products, and may also offer opportunities to apply for employment. We hope that you enjoy our site and will come back often to visit! **

When do we collect personal information?

** We only collect personally identifiable data, such as names, addresses, e-mail addresses, hobby or activity information, demographic information (age, gender, etc.), taste or preference information, and the like, when voluntarily submitted by a visitor. Visitors may choose to submit personal information to enter contests, to obtain information or submit a comment, to register for a loyalty program or chat room, or to place an order. We make a special effort to advise children to get parental permission before providing information or ordering anything on-line, and urge parents to supervise their children's on-line use. We may ask for age information from children so that we can provide age-relevant content and fulfill certain legal obligations; if we learn we are dealing with a young child, we may ask for the e-mail address of a parent and make an effort to contact them to determine if the child has permission to provide information to us. **

What do we do with the information?

** Providing personal information is up to you, our visitor. We collect personally identifiable information to e-mail you with updates and news, to respond to your questions or comments, to register you for certain features, and/or to send out brochures and other information on our products or our company. We ask visitors providing e-mail addresses to let us know if they would like further information or updates from us or our site; only those who request it will receive follow-up e-mail or other communications from us. Only those who expressly ask to receive such information online will get it. We also offer visitors an "opt-out" option at any time they wish to cease receiving e-mails or other information from us.

Personal information is used solely by us, and our affiliates, agents or business partners who help make this site and its content and the products and services at this site, available to you in order to respond to your requests (like fulfilling online shopping orders or offering a sweepstakes or promotion), and to better serve you, consistent with this policy. **

How do we use "cookies"?

What are cookies?

**Cookies are data files that a Web site sends to your computer while you are viewing the site. These data files include information that allows our site to remember important information that will make your use of the site more efficient and useful to you. Our sites use cookies for a variety of purposes. We use cookie technology and IP addresses to obtain non-personal information from on-line visitors, and also to provide registered visitors with the best possible personalized on-line experience. **

How do we use cookies?

**Visitors to our sites use different web browsers and different computers. To make your visits as easy as possible with the technology you use, we automatically keep track of the type of browser (e.g., Internet Explorer, Firefox) and operating system (e.g., Windows, Macintosh) used by a visitor, and the domain name of the visitor's Internet service provider. We also track the total number of visitors to our site in an aggregate form to allow us to update and improve our site; personally identifiable information is not extracted in this process. This data tells us if more visitors prefer certain features or areas to others, which helps us keep our site fresh and interesting to the majority of our visitors. **

What if I don't want cookies? 

**If you don't want cookies, you can set your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent or turn off all cookies through your browser (e.g., Internet Explorer or Firefox). (Check your browser HELP menu to learn the correct way to change or update your cookies.) If you disable cookies, you may be unable to access some of the features noted above. **

What about chat rooms, message boards, or other interactive forums? 

**We may offer chat rooms, message or bulletin boards, or interactive areas where visitors may post comments or information for our visitors enjoyment. As you know, anything you post online is available for the world to see. We make no representations and undertake no obligations as to information you voluntarily post. **

What do you do to safeguard personal information? 

**We have instituted safeguards to check that our internal procedures meet our high policy standards. We also use our best efforts to be sure that third parties who work with us as our agents to make this site and its contents available to you, and to fulfill your orders and requests, agree to protect personal information that they must access in order to serve our site and our visitors. **

What about links to other sites? 

**We may offer links to other sites outside Find Local Weather. However, we try to link only with sites that share our values. You should always check the privacy policy of any linked site to understand their information collection practices, including how they may use cookies. We are not responsible for the content or information collection policies of sites operated by other companies. If you visit another site, you should review their privacy and other policies. **

Anything else I should know? 

**We reserve the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request, to conduct investigations of consumer complaints or possible breaches of law, to protect the integrity of the site, to fulfill your requests, or to cooperate in any legal investigation. 

What should I do if I have questions, wish to access, update or delete information, or wish to opt out of receiving future communications? 

If you would like us to access, update, change, or delete information we have about you (subject to any applicable legal exceptions), would like to opt out of receiving further communications from us, or have questions about our privacy policy, please contact our Information Department... **[Contact Us](http://www.findlocalweather.com/contact.htm)**.
